## Gustav N. Bøgh

Born: 19th May 1998

Bispebjerg Parkallé 22

Emdrup 2400

Phone: +45 40573503

Email: gustavbogh@gmail.com

## Languages

English: FluentDanish: NativeSpanish: Beginner

• Scandinavian: Converse with Swedes and Norwegians

• German: Small conversation

## About me

My name is Gustav and I am 25 years old. My passion is web development, and I love working in the industry. I am currently studying Multimedia Design at KEA Academy. I see myself as a team player who likes to work with other people, I am devoted to my work and a quick learner. I am responsible, forthcoming, easy to work with, open, and then I love to work with new people.

## Personal Qualifications

- Devoted to my work
- Forthcoming
- Independent
- Flexible
- Conscientious
- Service minded
- Always positive
- Quick Learner
- Punctual
- Good under Pressure
- Fast Paced
- Honest

## Experience

## 2020 - Now Restaurant All-rounder – The Landing, Honeysuckle Dr, Newcastle NSW.

Duties include:

- Serving food (+3 plates)
- Serving high end Cocktails and Mocktails
- Serving Wine (Chardonnay, Riesling, Sauvignon Blanc, Merlot, Cabernet Sauvignon, Pinot Noir)
- Serving beer (Wheat, stout, bitters, IPA, brown ale...)
- Serving exclusive champagne
- Assisting Kitchen staff
- Handling Cashier
- Serving Coffee

## 2019 Bartender – Victoria Pub, Gammeltorv Cph.

**Duties Include:** 

- Serving drinks (Cocktails, Mocktails)
- Serving beer (Wheat, stout, bitters, IPA, brown ale...)
- Serving Wine (Chardonnay, Pinot Noir)
- Serving Snacks
- Table service
- Carrying 6 + Drinks on tray
- Handling Cashier

## Bartender – Royal Arena (Concert Hall) VIP

2019 Duties Include

- Serving high end Cocktail and Mocktails
- Serving Wine (Chardonnay, Riesling, Sauvignon Blanc, Merlot, Cabernet Sauvignon, Pinot Noir)
- Serving beer (Wheat, stout, bitters, IPA, brown ale...)
- Serving exclusive champagne
- Assisting Kitchen staff
- Handling Cashier

## Bartender and Waiter - Chabber.com (English speaking)

2016 – 2019 Duties include:

- Freelance Bartender/Waiter, 20+ Venues, Bars, Hotels, Cocktail bars, Restaurants
- Serving food (+3 plates)
- Serving high end Cocktails and Mocktails
- Serving Wine (Chardonnay, Riesling, Sauvignon Blanc, Merlot, Cabernet Sauvignon, Pinot Noir)
- Serving beer (Wheat, stout, bitters, IPA, brown ale...)
- Serving exclusive champagne
- Assisting Kitchen staff
- Handling Cashier

## Bartender and Waiter - Tribeca (Restaurant), Nørrebro Cph.

Duties include:

- Serving food (+3 plates)
- Serving high end Cocktails and Mocktails
- Serving Wine (Chardonnay, Riesling, Sauvignon Blanc, Merlot, Cabernet Sauvignon, Pinot Noir)
- Serving beer (Wheat, stout, bitters, IPA, brown ale...)
- Serving exclusive champagne

2018

- Assisting Kitchen staff
- Handling Cashier
- Acting as Barista, serving Coffee and Tea

#### 2017 - 2018

## Lodge waiter and Bartender - Odd Fellow Palæet, Cph. - Denmark

**Duties Include:** 

- Serving under oath
- Acting as Event manager
- Serving food (+3 plates)
- Serving high end Cocktails and Mocktails
- Serving Wine (Chardonnay, Riesling, Sauvignon Blanc, Merlot, Cabernet Sauvignon, Pinot Noir)
- Serving beer (Wheat, stout, bitters, IPA, brown ale...)
- Serving exclusive champagne
- Assisting Kitchen staff
- Handling Cashier
- Acting as Barista, serving Coffee and Tea

## 2016 - 2017 Leader/Key holder - Lokal Brugsen (supermarket), Virum - Denmark

Duties include:

- Young worker
  - Key holder
  - Assisting manager
  - Cashier
  - Filling shelfs and cleaning

## 2015-2016 Fakta (Supermarket), Lyngby Station – Denmark

Duties Include:

- Cashier
- Filling shelfs and cleaning

## Courses and Certificates

## Jan. 2020 **European Bartender School, 4 Weeks** – European

Bartender School Phuket – Thailand.

Professional bartender education with the following subjects and tests:

- Teamwork
- Bar cleanliness and hygiene
- commodity handling
- Guest focus
- Drink mixing techniques
- Serving techniques
- Free pouring and jigger skills
- Speed mixing
- Working and exhibition flair
- Accuracy and precision
- Stress management.

## Feb. 2020 "Clear to work" Beer Course – Australia:

## Course overview:

- History of Beer
- The beer brewing process
- The styles of beer
- Beer tasting and food matching
- Serving and selling beer
- Ciders

## "Clear to work" Wine Course - Australia:

#### Feb. 2020

#### Course overview:

- History of wine and wine Making
- Wine varieties and regions
- Wine tasting and food matching
- Selling wine

## "Clear to work" Barista Course - Australia

## Feb. 2020

#### Course overview:

- Organize coffee workstations
- Select and grind coffee beans
- Advise customers and take espresso orders
- Extract and monitor quality of espresso
- Undertake milk texturing process
- Serve espresso coffee beverages
- Clean espresso machine

# Feb. 2020 Responsible Service of Alcohol Certificate – department of industry, liquor and Gaming, NSW Australia.

## 2018

Bartender Diploma – Cocktail academy, Chabber Aps and Cocktailkursus.dk – Denmark

First Aid Certification – Danish Military/"Dansk Førstehjælpsråd"

## Education

2023 - now	KEA - Københavns Erhvervsakademi, Multimedia Design 1. Semester
2018 - 2019	Sergeant School (Non-commissioned junior officer) - Varde Kaserne (7 Month) – Danish Military
2018 - 2018	Værnepligt (National Military Service) – Aalborg Kaserne (4 Month) – Denmark
2015 – 2018	Virum Gymnasium 11, 12 and 13 <sup>th</sup> grade – Denmark
2014 - 2015	Kerteminde Efterskole 10 <sup>th</sup> grade (Danish boarding school)
2004 - 2014	Kongevejens Skole 09 <sup>th</sup> grade – Virum, Denmark